Rock on to your heart!
We are the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department!
Yes, I'm Kanami Tsujino aka Kanamin from Super Tokimeki Blue!
Yes, I'm Anjulia aka Juli, the Super Tokimeki Purple!
Yes, I'm Hitochan aka Hitoka Osakai, the Super Tokimeki Red!
Yes, I am Haruka Koizumi aka Oharu in Super Thrilling Pink!
Yes, I'm Akichan aka Sudake from Super Thrilling Lemon!
Yes, I'm Hiyori Yoshikawa aka Hiyori-n from Super Tokimeki Green!
Yes, the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department is a six-member idol group from Stardust Promotion!
Our motto is "Rock on to your heart! is our slogan!
In 2023, Suki, the super version will be the talk of the town on SNS
Suki, the super version of the song, became a hot topic on social networking sites such as TikTok and other music distribution sites, and reached No. 1 not only in Japan, but also overseas!
We want Suki to be a buzz from the beginning!
Ayurika really wants to spread the good songs that we love.
We didn't have the idea of making a buzz.
But after we got a lot of buzz on TikTok and people started dancing to the song
I was thinking, "I wonder if this song will get a lot of buzz.
I've been trying to find out if this choreography would get buzz.
Finally, the most adorable one is getting a little buzz.
We've even had students in school uniforms dancing to it.
It's like our song is popular when JKs are dancing to it.
It makes me happy.
Also, yesterday I happened to be on the train with Hughie, and the cutest thing came on the train.
I don't know if it was TikTok or what, but it just happened to play when I opened my phone.
I was so flustered I couldn't take it anymore.
I could feel that a lot of people were listening to it.
The most adorable thing is that the total number of views on TikTok has now exceeded 340 million.
I think the most important thing is that our cute dance moves are gaining popularity!
Next Preview
Next Trailer
preview of the next episode
next preview
Many celebrities have also posted videos using the song!
This song is a song about a broken heart.
This song is supposed to be a heartbreak song, but when you finish listening to it, you will feel very positive.
It's a song that gives you a great sense of self-affirmation.
The song was written by Ogasawara-san.
The endings are cute, the melody is cute, and there is a lot of cuteness in the song.
Anyway, it's filled with lots of cuteness!
I've been asking Ogasawara-san to compose a song for a long time.
I've been secretly asking the staff and others to have you compose a song for us for a long time.
When it came true, I thought it was just a dream.
I'm really happy about it.
I'm so happy that the members and fans celebrated with me.
I'm so happy for you.
It was really a dream come true.
For example, if you are a girl, you can listen to this song while you are doing your make-up.
If I listen to this song and have my makeup done
I would be even prettier and more positive.
It was very positive and motivating.
And even if you're not a girl
When you are faced with something negative...
I think it's a song that tells me that I can be more powerful.
I hope people of both sexes will listen to this song.
I want it to be a rhythm.
To be in the rhythm and to be in the rhythm
To ride on the rhythm
In the "Tokimeki Hana" tour, there is a part where you shoot a bow and arrow like this
there is a part where he shoots a bow and arrow like this.
If you wink at them
I think you'll be shot through.
Her upper body is cute, too.
but the song is also very cute when you dance with your whole body.
Even if you dance with your whole body, please lean your body as much as you can and dance big and cute.
I hope you dance big and cute!
In reference to the title of the song, I asked her to tell me the moment when she feels she is the cutest of all.
I bought some flowers the other day.
They say that even flowers have a heart.
So today morning, as I was changing the water
and tell the flowers they are pretty.
I always give them love and nurture them.
I want them to bloom beautifully for a long, long time.
So I told them they are pretty today too.
I left the house.
They're so cute!
I'm 22 and I'll be 23 this year.
I still sleep with my mom and sister.
So when I'm away on an expedition or something.
I feel a little lonely.
Is he cute?
So cute.
Whenever I find something good.
I buy one and share it with my mom.
Cute.
It's cute.
She's eating it.
Don't sleep alone.
If you bring home a gift or something, you can share it with your mom.
I share it with my mom.
I eat it while saying how delicious it is.
I still have a fear of flying.
I still get scared of airplanes unless a member of the group rides next to me.
I freeze up by myself.
This is what it looks like when you have a member of the group next to you.
This is how I get on the plane.
No, no, no.
I'm afraid of taking off.
If I don't have a member next to me...
I'm afraid of making a weird noise.
Like, "Whew!
Is he cute?
So cute!
Cute.
I made a shelf in my room.
I made a space for all my favorite things.
I really wanted to go look at it at night.
I got up and got out of bed alone in my room
And I'd linger on that shelf.
When I see something I like.
I want to see it in person and bathe in it.
It's a bit of a mystery.
Is he cute?
Cute.
I have a habit of reporting things.
I find something cute.
Or I find something delicious.
I have a habit of reporting everything
I have a habit of reporting it especially to Hiyori
Today, I'm going to change my LINE
I reported to Hiyori that I had changed my clothes.
I reported that I changed my clothes.
He said, "You changed your clothes!
I've been doing that for a long time, and I really go for it.
Cute?
Cute.
In July 2023, they performed at a festival in Indonesia for the first time!
Many overseas fans went crazy for the show!
Indonesia is the place where the skincho version
I heard that a lot of Indonesian people know us.
so we went to the festival.
When we sang the skincho version at the live
everyone sang in chorus from the beginning to the end.
It's not so common in Japan.
In Japan, it is common culture to call out to the audience.
But when we performed in Indonesia
everyone sang along with us even though we were singing in Japanese the whole time.
It was a new experience for us.
It was a surprise or a shock to us.
It was a lot of fun, and I want to go back.
It's normal to have a lot of cameras around.
It's the same during the show.
but also during the preparation and standby time before the show.
The lady who was cleaning up and stuff like that was rolling the camera
smiling and taking pictures of me.
That's why I was impressed that they never let their guard down anywhere.
When I went to Indonesia for MC, I tried my best to speak Indonesian.
I tried my best to speak in Indonesian.
So when I go there, I will try my best to speak in the language of that country.
I need to practice.
Give me the recording in your heart.
You know the greeting, "I'm going to give you a head start," right?
When I went to Indonesia, I did that in Indonesian version.
I also learned Indonesian, Korean, Japanese, and English versions.
I also learned the Indonesian, Korean, Japanese, and English versions of the greeting in foreign languages.
I hope I can go to Indonesia.
I hope we can go to Indonesia!
We've been pursuing a pretty royal idol style.
Our costumes are cute and shiny and frilly.
I feel like we are doing what we used to think of as the ideal idol.
I feel like we're doing what we've always wanted to do.
I think that's one of the strengths of the group.
And we don't mind doing it.
I think that's one of the strengths of our group.
I think that's what makes Tokiyo so appealing.
I think that's the charm of Tokisei.
Our dream is to perform at Saitama Super Arena.
Also, we are very happy to see that the cutest girls in this show are known overseas and in many other places.
I hope we can do an overseas tour someday.
We would also like to appear on TV more and more.
I hope that people will get to know not only our songs but also our members.
I want people to say that we are cute when we say we are cute.